# Romario Lourenco

1 Bramshaw Road, London • <a href="https://www.decibel.games/">https://www.decibel.games/</a> • <a href="linkedin.com/in/romariolourenco">linkedin.com/in/romariolourenco</a> romarioarlindo@gmail.com • +44 7507 941001

### **Design-Led Senior Product Manager**

Design-led, entrepreneurial product leader with over 7+ years of experience in design, marketing and product management. At GoDaddy, I led the internal content tooling team for their mobile cross-platform photo and video editor (Over, acquired). Increased metadata by 14% within 6 weeks; improved content discovery and user recommendations across Over and GoDaddy marketing suite.

Currently bootstrapping an audio gaming studio, creating innovative mobile audio games through immersive storytelling and play. Featured on the Apple App Store as 'New Games We Love' in +110 markets.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **Co-Founder**

Decibel Games • London, England, UK

October 2023 - Present

Decibel Games is a mobile audio games studio focused on creating immersive audio games for mobile, powered by Ai. Our vision is to become a global creator-led marketplace that challenges the conventional gaming industry through sound.

- Launched a trivia audio game powered by Ai; drove +2000 installs within 14 days. Ranked Top 30 across Trivia and Family
  game categories.
- Leading product development/agile methodologies, product design, go-to-market strategies and exploring new ideas for future titles Drove +2000 waitlist for our next title.
- Driving distribution through storefront optimisation and promotion; increased app installs by 10% week-on-week.

#### Senior Product Manager · Full-time

**BLOK** • London, England, UK

May 2022 - September 2023

BLOK is the leading UK hybrid fitness startup. As a seasoned collaborator, I led a cross-functional team to ship BLOK's cross-platform mobile experience to further drive revenue and customer growth.

- Launched iOS and Android cross-platform mobile apps, boosting reservations by 5.6% within 8 weeks and ensured product quality by maintaining a 4.7-star rating on App Store/Google Play.
- Designed and implemented internal systems to enhance operational efficiency, including an instructor payroll management system and a video content management system.
- Developed a mobile referral system, increasing new customer sales by 25% within two months. 36% month-on-month growth.

### **Product Manager · Full-time**

GoDaddy • London, England, UK

January 2021 - April 2022

Over (now known as GoDaddy Studio) is a mobile design app that was acquired by GoDaddy. I led the internal content tooling to accelerate content recommendations across Over and GoDaddy products.

- Led a team in accelerating content recommendations for Over & GoDaddy integrations.
- Developed vision, strategy, and product roadmap for content tooling, increasing metadata by 14% within 6 weeks; improved content discovery and user recommendations for photo and video editor.
- Established a user interview program for the Product function. Conducted over 100 sessions within 8 weeks to guide product decisions for photo and video editing tooling through user feedback.

## **Product Marketing Manager**

GoDaddy • London, England, UK

March 2020 - December 2020

- Integrated social channels, expanding GoDaddy's social audience by 66% and targeting a younger entrepreneurial audience.
- Developed a social strategy for GoDaddy's product suite, driving organic audience growth through collaboration with Brand Social team.

### **Product Marketing Manager · Full-time**

Over • London

July 2019 - February 2020

Over (now known as GoDaddy Studio) is a mobile design app that was acquired by GoDaddy. My role was to expand Over's social presence and drive community-led growth.

- Developed an ambassador/creator strategy resulting in +7,000 new users in 6 months and a 41% conversion rate from free-to-paid subscriptions.
- Executed a cross-channel social strategy and content design to expand our organic audience, leading to a 44% increase in our Instagram following while maintaining high engagement rates.

### Marketing Manager · Full-time

Orderin • Cape Town

February 2018 - June 2019

Orderin was South Africa's first food delivery e-commerce startup. My role involved sales generation, brand development, user research, and usability testing.

Drove a 5% weekly GMV increase through promotional materials and achieved a 12% open rate hike via A/B testing.

## **Product Designer · Full-time**

Fonk • Cape Town

December 2016 - January 2018

Fonk is a mobile development agency in Cape Town and Amsterdam. I worked on a variety of B2B and B2C SaaS products.

· Managed design sprints for 10 clients, resulting in seven proceeding with product development.

**EDUCATION** 

## **BComm in Marketing And Financial Management**

University of Stellenbosch • South Africa

January 2014 - December 2021

**CERTIFICATIONS** 

## **Product Management Fundamentals**

March 2021 - April 2024

Reforge

## **Mastering Product Management**

January 2022 - February 2024

Reforge

#### **SKILLS & INTERESTS**

Agile Methodology, Android, Content Creation, Content Management, Cross Functional Skills, Cross Platform Development, Data Analysis, Engagement Strategy, Figma, Go To Market Strategy, iOS, JIRA, KPIs, Leadership, Lifecycle Management, Market Analysis, Market Research, OKRs, Product Demos, Product Development, Product Discovery, Product Leadership, Product Management, Product Marketing, Product Strategy, Product Vision, QA, Quantitative And Qualitative Insights, Revenue Generation, Root Cause Analysis, Social Media, Strategy and Vision, User Experience, User Research, Wireframe sketching, Cooking up a storm, Learning French, Listening to music and podcasts, Photographing architecture, Reading about business, Running the streets of London, Surfing the App Store